{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044359469","data":{"timestamp":" 947044359469"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044359693","data":{"timestamp":" 947044359693"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044360656","data":{"timestamp":" 947044360656"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044361929","data":{"timestamp":" 947044361929"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044364784","data":{"timestamp":" 947044364784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044365626","data":{"timestamp":" 947044365626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044365939","data":{"timestamp":" 947044365939"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044367171","data":{"timestamp":" 947044367171"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044370635","data":{"timestamp":" 947044370634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044371617","data":{"timestamp":" 947044371617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044371870","data":{"timestamp":" 947044371869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044372813","data":{"timestamp":" 947044372813"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044375620","data":{"timestamp":" 947044375620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044376653","data":{"timestamp":" 947044376653"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044377125","data":{"timestamp":" 947044377125"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044381623","data":{"timestamp":" 947044381623"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044381679","data":{"timestamp":" 947044381679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6aff9de5-7514-460b-9c3d-533c4e8812e2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044412139","data":{"timestamp":" 947044412139"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" e94f9777-6703-4a96-8500-86f1a9b80ef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" PALESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044432981","data":{"timestamp":" 947044432981"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" e94f9777-6703-4a96-8500-86f1a9b80ef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044433053","data":{"timestamp":" 947044433053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" e94f9777-6703-4a96-8500-86f1a9b80ef3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" PALESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044445202","data":{"timestamp":" 947044445202"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 9e479e03-510e-4d3e-8848-fbf6f2488ae5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" PALESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044492266","data":{"timestamp":" 947044492266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 9e479e03-510e-4d3e-8848-fbf6f2488ae5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" PALESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044493808","data":{"timestamp":" 947044493808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 9e479e03-510e-4d3e-8848-fbf6f2488ae5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044497810","data":{"timestamp":" 947044497809"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 9e479e03-510e-4d3e-8848-fbf6f2488ae5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044497898","data":{"timestamp":" 947044497898"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 9e479e03-510e-4d3e-8848-fbf6f2488ae5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044530674","data":{"timestamp":" 947044530674"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6ceb5380-2a76-4548-8e46-c62d1e6c80d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044533878","data":{"timestamp":" 947044533878"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 6ceb5380-2a76-4548-8e46-c62d1e6c80d2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044546116","data":{"timestamp":" 947044546115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" PALESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044556678","data":{"timestamp":" 947044556677"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" palesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALESA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044558284","data":{"timestamp":" 947044558283"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044562999","data":{"timestamp":" 947044562999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044564589","data":{"timestamp":" 947044564588"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044567996","data":{"timestamp":" 947044567996"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044569578","data":{"timestamp":" 947044569577"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROSA"," userResponse":" ROSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044580617","data":{"timestamp":" 947044580617"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" rosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ROSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044582220","data":{"timestamp":" 947044582219"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044586462","data":{"timestamp":" 947044586462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044588015","data":{"timestamp":" 947044588015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044619679","data":{"timestamp":" 947044619679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044621240","data":{"timestamp":" 947044621240"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" LISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044646542","data":{"timestamp":" 947044646541"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044648142","data":{"timestamp":" 947044648141"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::end.wrd.sa.rand.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044650162","data":{"timestamp":" 947044650161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044650246","data":{"timestamp":" 947044650246"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 21a50058-f8a0-4b5f-a7a1-a96bdfb20f1f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__end.wrd.sa.rand.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044658681","data":{"timestamp":" 947044658680"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044658913","data":{"timestamp":" 947044658912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044659886","data":{"timestamp":" 947044659885"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044661176","data":{"timestamp":" 947044661175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044664132","data":{"timestamp":" 947044664131"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044664990","data":{"timestamp":" 947044664989"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044665308","data":{"timestamp":" 947044665308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044666552","data":{"timestamp":" 947044666551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044670135","data":{"timestamp":" 947044670135"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044671133","data":{"timestamp":" 947044671132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044671395","data":{"timestamp":" 947044671394"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044672351","data":{"timestamp":" 947044672350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044675250","data":{"timestamp":" 947044675249"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044676291","data":{"timestamp":" 947044676290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044676772","data":{"timestamp":" 947044676771"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044681300","data":{"timestamp":" 947044681299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044681419","data":{"timestamp":" 947044681419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 3772f30d-ae7a-48b3-8246-0a05cdb65ef4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044694364","data":{"timestamp":" 947044694364"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044694598","data":{"timestamp":" 947044694597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044695576","data":{"timestamp":" 947044695575"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044696859","data":{"timestamp":" 947044696858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044699779","data":{"timestamp":" 947044699778"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044700634","data":{"timestamp":" 947044700633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044700955","data":{"timestamp":" 947044700954"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044702197","data":{"timestamp":" 947044702197"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044705822","data":{"timestamp":" 947044705820"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044706808","data":{"timestamp":" 947044706808"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044707069","data":{"timestamp":" 947044707069"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044708038","data":{"timestamp":" 947044708038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044710945","data":{"timestamp":" 947044710944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044711984","data":{"timestamp":" 947044711984"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044712462","data":{"timestamp":" 947044712462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044717039","data":{"timestamp":" 947044717038"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044717150","data":{"timestamp":" 947044717150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" f083f436-9b90-423a-82e1-fa3ec37a2107"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044729908","data":{"timestamp":" 947044729907"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044730143","data":{"timestamp":" 947044730142"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044731116","data":{"timestamp":" 947044731115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044732401","data":{"timestamp":" 947044732401"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044735352","data":{"timestamp":" 947044735352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044736206","data":{"timestamp":" 947044736205"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044736525","data":{"timestamp":" 947044736524"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044737767","data":{"timestamp":" 947044737767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044741344","data":{"timestamp":" 947044741343"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044742342","data":{"timestamp":" 947044742341"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044742606","data":{"timestamp":" 947044742605"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044743557","data":{"timestamp":" 947044743557"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044746396","data":{"timestamp":" 947044746395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044747439","data":{"timestamp":" 947044747439"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044747917","data":{"timestamp":" 947044747917"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044752464","data":{"timestamp":" 947044752463"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044752588","data":{"timestamp":" 947044752587"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" b00c9cfa-2e20-4f14-98c3-9f6cc499ca0c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044767797","data":{"timestamp":" 947044767797"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044768034","data":{"timestamp":" 947044768034"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044769010","data":{"timestamp":" 947044769009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044770300","data":{"timestamp":" 947044770299"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044773220","data":{"timestamp":" 947044773218"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044774068","data":{"timestamp":" 947044774067"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044774388","data":{"timestamp":" 947044774387"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044775637","data":{"timestamp":" 947044775636"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044779244","data":{"timestamp":" 947044779243"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044780242","data":{"timestamp":" 947044780241"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044780501","data":{"timestamp":" 947044780500"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044781452","data":{"timestamp":" 947044781451"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044784382","data":{"timestamp":" 947044784381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044785428","data":{"timestamp":" 947044785428"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044785911","data":{"timestamp":" 947044785910"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044790426","data":{"timestamp":" 947044790425"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044790503","data":{"timestamp":" 947044790503"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 5c331294-6a68-4247-a187-85079aa6e267"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044806492","data":{"timestamp":" 947044806491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044806726","data":{"timestamp":" 947044806725"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044807700","data":{"timestamp":" 947044807700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044808993","data":{"timestamp":" 947044808992"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044811868","data":{"timestamp":" 947044811867"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044812724","data":{"timestamp":" 947044812723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044813043","data":{"timestamp":" 947044813042"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044814286","data":{"timestamp":" 947044814285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044817863","data":{"timestamp":" 947044817862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044818859","data":{"timestamp":" 947044818858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044819123","data":{"timestamp":" 947044819122"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044820081","data":{"timestamp":" 947044820080"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044822960","data":{"timestamp":" 947044822960"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044824004","data":{"timestamp":" 947044824003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044824485","data":{"timestamp":" 947044824485"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044829048","data":{"timestamp":" 947044829047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044829138","data":{"timestamp":" 947044829138"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" d635f6d7-4948-4e8f-b3c2-f9d5e1ad175f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044861263","data":{"timestamp":" 947044861263"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kasa_kasa-yowe-watu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kasa"," userResponse":" kasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044874071","data":{"timestamp":" 947044874071"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kosa_muda-aina-kosa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kosa"," userResponse":" kosa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044883966","data":{"timestamp":" 947044883966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sisa_sisa-maji-kana"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sisa"," userResponse":" sisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044913193","data":{"timestamp":" 947044913193"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_kapu-hasa-dada"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044951182","data":{"timestamp":" 947044951182"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lisa_jike-lisa-humo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lisa"," userResponse":" lisa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044995151","data":{"timestamp":" 947044995151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_naro-hasa-lima"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045038792","data":{"timestamp":" 947045038792"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hasa_hasa-nono-kuoa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hasa"," userResponse":" hasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045159175","data":{"timestamp":" 947045159175"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_giza-sare-sasa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sasa"," userResponse":" sasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045245144","data":{"timestamp":" 947045245143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_elsa_elsa-kato-miye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" elsa"," userResponse":" elsa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045260571","data":{"timestamp":" 947045260571"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_pana-sasa-anga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sasa"," userResponse":" sasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.sa.noShow.30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045266312","data":{"timestamp":" 947045266311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_pana-sasa-anga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:5..15.off1.3__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045286902","data":{"timestamp":" 947045286901"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 62ecf1d1-fd71-4785-84e4-9e93b1bf151c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.sa.noShow.30"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_sasa_pana-sasa-anga"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045331271","data":{"timestamp":" 947045331270"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045332353","data":{"timestamp":" 947045332352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045335590","data":{"timestamp":" 947045335590"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045336630","data":{"timestamp":" 947045336630"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kukosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOSA"," userResponse":" KUKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045341329","data":{"timestamp":" 947045341328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045342398","data":{"timestamp":" 947045342398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" makosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKOSA"," userResponse":" MAKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045347402","data":{"timestamp":" 947045347402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045348444","data":{"timestamp":" 947045348443"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" lisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LISA"," userResponse":" LISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045352132","data":{"timestamp":" 947045352132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045353177","data":{"timestamp":" 947045353176"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pesa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PESA"," userResponse":" PESA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045356180","data":{"timestamp":" 947045356179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045356269","data":{"timestamp":" 947045356268"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045357305","data":{"timestamp":" 947045357305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045359829","data":{"timestamp":" 947045359828"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kosa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOSA"," userResponse":" KOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045362570","data":{"timestamp":" 947045362569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISA"," userResponse":" KISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045363627","data":{"timestamp":" 947045363626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISA"," userResponse":" KISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045372380","data":{"timestamp":" 947045372380"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045373429","data":{"timestamp":" 947045373429"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045376312","data":{"timestamp":" 947045376311"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045376551","data":{"timestamp":" 947045376551"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TISA"," userResponse":" TISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::end.wrd.sa.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045385336","data":{"timestamp":" 947045385335"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 8297d9cf-04de-40ce-b70a-52c0f89d081e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__end.wrd.sa.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" tisa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045394639","data":{"timestamp":" 947045394639"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045394862","data":{"timestamp":" 947045394862"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045395826","data":{"timestamp":" 947045395826"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045397112","data":{"timestamp":" 947045397112"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045400034","data":{"timestamp":" 947045400033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045400894","data":{"timestamp":" 947045400893"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045401215","data":{"timestamp":" 947045401215"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045402462","data":{"timestamp":" 947045402461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045406030","data":{"timestamp":" 947045406029"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045407028","data":{"timestamp":" 947045407027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045407288","data":{"timestamp":" 947045407288"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045408242","data":{"timestamp":" 947045408242"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045411186","data":{"timestamp":" 947045411186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045412226","data":{"timestamp":" 947045412225"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045412707","data":{"timestamp":" 947045412706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045417312","data":{"timestamp":" 947045417310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045417424","data":{"timestamp":" 947045417424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 776437db-4a07-46f9-8b46-4aa88add5880"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.end.sa.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947045480651","data":{"timestamp":" 947045480651"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_065158"," gameId":" 54bfa8d9-4563-4942-b79a-6e7cffdda9cc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.end.sa.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write___sa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" ","":"<empty>"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}